Hello everyone, we will introduce two tools that are powerful in both functions and are related to each other, which only help you to deal with 2D measurement, measurement point computer and computer department.
The measurement point computer is the work area where you create a mathematical formula, and the computer department is the record and management center for these results.
First of all, let's take a look at the measurement point computer. It is a dynamic interface that is used to perform mathematical calculations directly on your clothing measurement point and link your formula to a 3D project, so that you do not need an external electronic table.
Next, let's take a look at how to visit the measurement point computer and navigate to the object window in the upper right corner of the screen. Click to open the measurement point label page.
The first way is to click to open the measurement point computer icon and open the computer window. Note that an empty computer will be opened at this time.
The second way is to click to open the measurement point icon and open the computer window. Note that an empty computer will be opened at this time.
The third way is to click to open the measurement point icon and open the computer window in the upper left corner of the screen.
The fourth way is to click to open the measurement point icon and open the computer window in the upper right corner of the screen. Note that an empty computer will be open at this time.
We will each type the measurement points variation points into the measuring technique tool.
Then let's learn how to use the measurement point computer.
First, open thecloud calculator icon. Click to open the measurement points version.
Click on the second measurement value, add it to the formula, you can also add a self-defined measurement value in the mathematical operation.
If the input is wrong, click on the C button on the calculator to empty the input.
Now we will use the three different measurement points created to do the calculation.
Press the return key or equal button to complete the calculation.
Then press the application, the calculation will be added as a measurement point to the automatically opened computer.
Now let's take a look at the computer. It is a special window for storage management and display.
All formulas for using the measurement point calculator are visited by the computer.
In addition to the application that was just introduced, it can also be redirected to the top menu bar.
Click on the 2D menu and select the computer from the drop-down list.
Click and drag the corner of the window to adjust its size to save screen space.
You can click on the arrow icon in the title bar to minimize the window to only display the title.
Prevent it from blocking your board.
In the default folder named default folder, check your calculation results.
Click on the add folder button next to the update to create a new folder.
Right-click and select the target folder to move the measurement value.
The trash can icon after clicking on the folder folder can delete the folder.
By double-clicking on the name, input the name you need, then press the return key to confirm.
To rename your calculation folder name.
If you have adjusted your board or measurement point measurement value.
Click on the update button at the top of the calculation.
You can manually refresh the data to reflect the new size.
Click on the measurement point icon next to the specific calculation.
You can add this calculation as a new measurement point to the measurement point label in the object window.
By clicking on the calculator icon next to the new added calculation measurement point.
This measurement point can be used in other calculations like a normal measurement point.
Click on the delete icon to delete a calculation.
But please note that this will not delete the object window.
Click on the code icon.
You can check the measurement value in all code sizes such as M, L, and XL.
By using the measurement point calculator to create a calculation formula.
And use the computing department to manage your calculation information.
You can maintain high-level technical accuracy throughout the design process.
We all know that the rule of thumb is very important for food supply.
It is important to achieve perfect shape.
In the previous version software, you can reduce the number of parts that have positive or negative optimizations to the version application.
But the rate of reduction is not easy to eliminate.
Now by updating the scanning machine, you not only can increase the number of parts, but also have the examinatory use of scanning tool.
Once you select this tool, the grid structure of all panels will be automatically displayed in the 2D window.
At the same time, there will be a new
animation setting, which will allow you to select the right size for each panel.
The size and hardness of the scale can be adjusted by clicking the icon on the top right.
For the suit, we often pull the front big body and the front sleeve.
So let's add some scale effects in the 3D.
Maintain the mode as increase, and keep the scale as positive.
To achieve the pull effect, turn on simulation, and click and drag on the target area of the panel.
If you are not satisfied with this effect, you can repeat it many times.
Continue to maintain the mode to increase, but the shrink rate will be changed to negative to achieve the
original state.
In addition, if you want to repeat theEPA effect, you only need to right-click on the EPA and select
the EPA selected by the delete option.
If you right-click on an EPA, you can also find the option to delete all EPAs, which makes
it very easy for you to repeat the EPAs all over again.
As you can see, the EPA tool in the 2026.0 version provides a more intuitive and accurate
way to delete EPAs.
You can use this method to delete the EPAs.
As you can see, the EPA tool in the 2026.0 version provides a more intuitive and accurate
to deal with the fabric.
Whether it is to fine-tune the sleeves or to adjust the
fabric, it is important to improve the performance of the fabric so that it can be used in the
future.
The first is to conduct a trial with the left and right side and the opposite is to check
that the design of the fabric is in the right position.
Next, the second step is to sync the fabric with the right and left sides to make sure it
From the 2D tool bar, select the hook outline tool, now move the light bar to the board, you can now select the basic line from the two sides of the symmetrical board, the inner line or the outer line of the board, press the Shift key to select the two sides of the board, you can see that you can now select the symmetrical line at the same time.
After completing the selection of the required line, right-click on the line displayed in any height, select the hook as a board from the pop-up menu, and place the new board in any blank area in the 2D window.
If you look at the newly created board, you will see that the symmetrical link is already in the active state and matches the original board.
This eliminates additional operation steps after the hook is removed, or the additional operation steps are opened, so that your physical window remains tight and your work process is not interrupted.
In the 2026.0 version, the hook function has been improved to improve the efficiency of work, and the most significant change in all updates is the irregular hook editing in the multi-line selection state.
Now let's take a look at this faster and more efficient hook operation process.
First, select the hook tool in the 2D tool bar on the right side of the 2D window from the 2D window, and click on the line or point to adjust the hook.
Then the hook table will appear on the right side of the property hook.
Now let's try the single block selection method after the update.
To select a continuous range of single blocks, first click on the first paragraph, then press the Shift key and click on the last paragraph.
As you can see, all the single blocks in the middle will immediately show a high number.
If you want to modify the specific values ​​of each non-continuous, please press the Ctrl key, MacOS user as the Command key, and click on each required paragraph.
Or more objectively, you can click and drag the mouse to the left to quickly select multiple single blocks.
After selecting a single block, press the Shift key or Ctrl key and double-click on the last single block.
The input frame will be activated. You can modify all selected areas at the same time.
All you need to do is enter the required code value and press the return key.
The value will be immediately applied to all selected code characters.
Through this multi-line selection function, you can shorten the time required to enter complex code values.
The function is now more flexible and convenient than before.
The following two practical updates under the checkbox editor are to increase your workflow efficiency.
First, in the checkbox, we usually put virtual models of various sizes side by side, so that they can be compared clearly.
This is to adjust the settings between virtual models and their costumes.
It is X-axis distance.
Previously, X-axis distance was calculated based on the center point of the virtual model.
This means that virtual models and costumes with large sizes may appear to be too close or even overlap.
In order to solve this problem, you may need to manually adjust the frame every time.
Let's take a look at how this has changed through the actual costume layout.
We have prepared a total of six sizes of virtual models and T-shirts with complete sizes.
Turn to the main menu bar at the top.
Select Production, then press the checkbox to open the window.
To check all the contents at once, please click on the second icon in the tool on the left.
Switch to the全景视图.
I will also enlarge the window so that you can see it clearly.
Now all the sizes are visible on one page.
In the lower right corner, you will find the X-axis distance menu.
You can set the distance between virtual models here.
Now let's adjust this value.
Please take a closer look at the changes on the screen.
I will set the X-axis distance value to 0.
In the previous version, the X-axis distance was calculated from the center axis of the virtual model.
But it is now calculated based on the border frame and the outer edge of the virtual model and costume combination.
In the past, the costume of one XXL size may overlap with the size of the X-axis next to it.
But as you can see now, even if it is a larger size, the distance between each size can also be based on the border frame and the outer edge.
So no matter what the body shape of the virtual model is, because the actual visible diameter remains unchanged, you no longer need to manually increase the diameter between the large sizes.
You can now comfortably check the number of results, and there will be no more overlap problems.
This calculation standard change will provide great convenience for anyone who wants to check the size of the cross-section.
The next step is to improve the view of the whole scene in the view of the horse.
Or use this T-shape as an example.
In the previous version, the camera lens change will cause the T-shape in the middle to look straight,
and the T-shape near the edge will look slanted or curved.
You can also see this transformation from the side view,
and as the number of horses increases, this change becomes more obvious.
However, after the update, from the smallest horse on the left to the largest horse on the right,
all the horses have the same front cross-section view,
just like the style view placed on the brand.
Since they are lined up straight and there are no changes,
it is easier to compare whether the horse is balanced or whether a specific expansion has been transformed.
When you need to check the slightly difference in the length of the sleeve or the bottom,
you no longer need to rotate the camera to find the correct angle.
You just need to look at the view of the whole scene directly in the picture.
This kind of view can be changed.
This kind of view is consistent and will definitely save you a lot of time.
In this update, we will introduce the expansion function of the T-shape,
which only helps to improve the efficiency of the film work.
First, choose to edit the T-shape tool in the middle of the 2D window tool bar,
then right-click the existing T-shape and select the link path from the menu.
Next, click the target you want the T-shape to be added to.
The guide line only appears when the T-shape tool is activated or the T-shape is selected.
Therefore, it will not interfere with your work area.
The T-shape after the link path will follow the T-shape line or the T-shape line.
T-shape can be linked to the T-shape line or the T-shape line.
If you want to remove the link path,
you only need to right-click the T-shape again and choose to remove the link path.
By using this function,
especially for complex work processes or projects with multiple numbers,
you can prevent the T-shape from being corrected during the correction of the T-shape,
and you can make corrections and correct the T-shape to join the work area better.
Now, I want to show you how to change the T-shape to the T-shape of the T-shape with aранe.
This is what you should do.
In the page of T-shape,
select the T-shape 1.
It is shown that the T-shape is connected to the T-shape after one click of the T-shape line.